Hi, I'm Dominic Waite, founder of
CaribNexus AI, this is CaribBooks,
an AI bookkeeper that works entirely in
WhatsApp, and what you're looking at right now
is a view of the dashboard that is
available to an accounting firm.
So when you take a look here to your left
and to your right, you're seeing a navigation
bar for Barrett Wynter & Associates,
that's the name of your accounting
firm will appear there.
You're also seeing the overview section that
is in a wider section over to your right,
where you're seeing the number
of active clients that you have,
you're seeing transaction pool, you're seeing
quick actions and we send CB activity across
all of your various clients.
This is a condensed view of everything that
is happening within your organisation.
Now I want to head into what are
the features of this dashboard.
I'm going to head into clients.
Clients specifically is a section of your
dashboard where you'll be able to see all of
the clients that you have within your organisation,
these are the clients that your accounting
practice serves, as well as a wider section
where you can be able to see overview,
transactions, reports, messages,
chart of accounts, capacity,
invoices, and bills.
Now I'm going to go in and scope specifically
to Ocho Rios Tours & Excursions,
just to show you exactly
how this looks for them.
You'll be able to see an overview and the
recent transactions that CB would have handled
for your specific client, all of
their transactions will show up here.
If you want to see a more granular view of
all of their transactions, you can go through
the transactions tab and see every
transaction that Ocho Rios Tours & Excursions
did. You can also be able to go through
and pull any one of 11 reports for them,
ranging from a GL register to transaction detail to profit
and loss, balance sheet, trial balance, AR aging, AP aging,
account ledger, expense breakdown.
It is all there for you to pull, let me kind
of show you exactly what that looks like.
So CaribBooks, reports, transaction detail,
you can go through and download a PDF or
an Excel sheet for any one
of, for the specific report.
You can also pull for
trial balance as well,
as CB manages trial balance.
Profit and loss works the
same way as well. GL register
works that same way as well.
You can also pull a balance sheet.
So that is available as well to
all of your organisation for any
one of your specific clients
you want to put a report for.
Now, let's just head into messages.
Messages is the back and forth
interaction between CB and your client.
You can be able to go through all
of those messages available there.
As for chart of accounts,
once it is that you're onboarding a client via
add new client, you will be able to actually
create a chart of accounts either by allowing
CB to create a chart of accounts based
off of the information that you provided
during signup, which we will get into.
And also as it pertains to
you, you can also import a
chart of accounts from QuickBooks and then
make adjustments if necessary and updates.
Of course, you're seeing
assets, liabilities,
capital, revenue and expenses.
You can be able to remove any one of the
entries or add an entry if needs be to any
one of the features.
And then you'll be able to update and CB will be
acting from that updated chart of accounts. Now,
as it pertains to capacity,
when it pertains to capacity,
remember your organisation, as
stated before, from your dashboard,
you will be able to have
300 transactions that is
available to you during
signup before any allocation.
In clients, when you go into capacity, this
is the place where you allocate transactions
to them. So, for example, let us say
you're working with a client and you know,
based on their business relationship or any
information that you've gathered for them,
that they will have up to 20
transactions for the month.
You can approve them for 20
out of the pool that you have.
20 from that 300 will leave 280 for you
to split across any other of your clients
within your organisation.
For this case that you need more, you can
order more capacity for your organisation that
way. But this is how you specifically scope
transactions by adjusting their capacity.
If, you know, Blue Mountain Roasters grow
and they reach up to 30 transactions for the
month, you can update your allocation.
Updating their allocation will, you know, go
into your pool and then give them an extra
10 on top of what they
had previously there.
And that is exactly how their
capacity updates in real time.
So, that's how that works for the features
for showing you how to, you know,
view and make edits and changes to
any one of your existing clients.
As it pertains now to adding a new client,
you can actually go and go through
the workflow to add in a new client.
I'm just going to go through
and speed through this workflow.
This is just going to be like randomized
information, just to show you exactly
what the workflow looks like.
Threadia AI onboarding it as
a software or tech services.
Does this business do? Just put
it in some information there.
You'd be describing what this business is,
how do their customer pay, whether
it be cash in hand, bank transfer,
invoice, card upholds, whatever you want to
put there, depending on the specific client.
What banks do they use? NCB, First Global.
Where is this business located?
What do they sell, services?
Do they own any business assets?
Business owner financing, just what number you have
options available for bank loan and vehicle financing,
mortgages. How's the business set up?
It's a limited company.
Supplies from credit.
Continue. GCT registered. Yes.
Customers on payroll. Yes.
Now we're to a very good point in the
onboarding process, where you see who
represents this business.
This person will message CB on your
WhatsApp line about this business.
What I really want to state firstly is that
once it is that you sign up for CaribBooks,
you'll be able to associate your WhatsApp
business account to your dashboard.
That WhatsApp business account will
have a specific number and then every
client that you onboard via the new
client will be manually approved to
text that phone number. Therefore,
CB will not respond to anyone's phone number that
is not a registered business within this portal.
They have to have a business profile that
you're actually creating right now so that
CB can respond contextually from.
In this case, we have a full name.
Full name in this case,
I'm just put Dominic Waite.
I'm putting a random number.
It's MSA. It's just a random number there.
I am the owner and you continue and then you
determine how much capacity to approve for
this new business initially.
In this case, you can approve up to 20.
It will actually take from the
available pool of 165 and leave 145
out of 300 remaining for any other of your
existing or new clients that you will onboard.
Now, to set up your account, you
will need a chart of accounts.
You have two options that are available for
you whether or not you want CB to create
a chart of accounts based off the information
that you just provided in the workflow.
It's a recommended option and then after it
generates the account, it will show up in
the chart of accounts tab in any
one of your specific clients.
I did show you that before or you can import
from QuickBooks a CSV sheet and then make
edits or improvements if needs be from
there and then same for generate for me.
CB will create a draft and then you can
approve and then make edits if needs be.
It will show up specifically in the chart
of accounts. We don't allow you to sit
down and wait until the chart is actually
completed. The moment you click generate
for me and the work starts happening in the
background and then the
workflow is completed.
Then after some time, probably in the next
two minutes, you can check and see the chart
of accounts that was created from CB like
this and then you'll be able to actually just
go through it, make changes if needs be,
additions or improvements if needs be.
Or if you already had this client working
around QuickBooks, import their CSV sheet for
their existing chart of accounts and bam,
you're right in there to be able to just allow
CB to see that chart of accounts and make
edits and changes accordingly from there on
then. So that is how you can see and manage
your existing clients and add a new client.
Heading over to the connect section,
remember I stated before once it is that you
sign up for CaribBooks, you are given the
option to connect a
WhatsApp business account.
Of course, you will need
a SIM card or an eSIM.
You create a WhatsApp
business account with it.
Whether it be an existing SIM that you have,
a SIM card or eSIM or a new one that you
purchase from any mobile carrier store,
you'll be able to actually just associate
a WhatsApp business account with it.
There is a QR code that actually will show
up here once it is you put in a number.
You scan that QR code as if you're
scanning from your phone and
then that WhatsApp account will be
associated with CB for CB to act within.
So all of your clients will text that phone
number and once it is that they have a business
account as indicated, if they sign up through add
a new client, CB will be able to see their name,
see who represent this business and then
talk to them and do transactions for them.
And any one of the transactions that they have
to report will show up in recent transactions.
You can download your reports and do what
to do with all of what I've just showed you
before in this demonstration.
So that is exactly what CaribBooks
represents in a nutshell.
Of course, you will be able
to go into your settings.
You will have a profile profile.
You'll also have your billing information,
your card, your invoices will show up here.
You can buy transactions
for your organisation.
So if it is a case that
you want to upgrade,
you can upgrade your plan or you can
buy transactions on demand as well.
So our starter plan up to 300
transactions for the month start at $99.
For growth, it's $169 up to
a thousand transactions.
Of course, if you upgrade, all of that will
be shown in your overview and then you will
be able to approve and create new clients
and then be able to dedicate and divide and
allocate your existing transaction
goals to your existing and new clients.
And that's exactly what
the dashboard represents.
It's a portal for you to be able
to log into, get your dashboard.
You'll be able to see all of the
clients that you have specifically.
You'll be able to download reports,
see updates, manage your clients
capacity that they have,
and even make updates if needs be.
And that is exactly what
it looks like here.
That's it. Thank you again for taking
the time to look at this video.
I hope you have yourself a wonderful day.
If you do need to get in touch with us,
please message us on
WhatsApp at 1 876 770 6900
You can also send me an email at
D-O-M-I-N-I-C W-A-I-T-E at caribnexusai.com
which is D O M I N I C dot
W A I T E at CaribNexus,
C A R I B N E X U X AI com You can also
message me on LinkedIn as
well, Dominic A R Waite,
and let me know your concerns as well as
your interest in this product as well.
And if you have any further questions,
concerns, or comments to raise,
please raise them with me.
With that said, thank you again for
taking the time to look at this video.
I hope you have yourself a
wonderful day. Take care.